{
    "subject": "Wendi_Deng",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Rupert_Murdoch",
    "human_readable": "Wendi Deng is married to Rupert Murdoch.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9705538749694824,
            "question": "When did Wendi Deng and Rupert Murdoch get married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9323230981826782,
            "question": "Are there any known children from the marriage of Rupert Murdoch and Wendi Deng?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9107049703598022,
            "question": "Who is Wendi Deng married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8698441386222839,
            "question": "Is Rupert Murdoch currently married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8310725092887878,
            "question": "To whom was Wendi Deng previously married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6944529414176941,
            "question": "What is the name of Rupert Murdoch's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.683323085308075,
            "question": "Who is Wendi Deng?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48590075969696045,
            "question": "Is there a significant age difference between Rupert Murdoch and Wendi Deng?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30291783809661865,
            "question": "Where did Wendi Deng grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20413462817668915,
            "question": "What are some of Rupert Murdoch's business ventures?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Wendi Deng is married to Rupert Murdoch.",
            "html": "yago_29897_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Wendi Deng grow up?",
            "html": "yago_29897_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a significant age difference between Rupert Murdoch and Wendi Deng?",
            "html": "yago_29897_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Wendi Deng?",
            "html": "yago_29897_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29897_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29897_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29897_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29897_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29897_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29897_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29897_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29897_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29897_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29897_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the marriage between Wendi Deng and Rupert Murdoch, stating that they were married from 1999 to 2013, had two children together, and Deng was described as Murdoch's third wife. This supports the triple \"Wendi Deng is married to Rupert Murdoch.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple sources state they were married from 1999 to 2013, indicating a past marriage.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}